A Guide to the Harrisonburg Historic Map Collection, 1873-1982 (bulk 1903-1956): SC 0050
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Series 2: Maps, 1903-1982 1903-1956
  - John Gray Paul to the City of Harrisonburg (New Reservoir, Washington St.), 1923 (Box OV 3, Folder 1)
  - Lots Owned by Jno.E.Sullivan (Water Street, Liberty Street), 1923 (Box OV 3, Folder 1)
  - Map of Haas 2nd Addition to Harrisonburg copy 1 & 2, 1923-1926 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Brock and Myers 2nd Addition to Harrisonburg, 1924 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Map of Dry River from Intake of Harrisonburg Water System to Bridgewater VA Showing Property Lines as Evidenced by Fences etc., 1924 (Storage 1, Box 1)
  - Map of Proposed Exchange of Land Between R.G. Alexander and the City of Harrisonburg (Main St, Paul St), 1924 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Mrs. Cornelia Switzer Burkholder to Mrs. Mary Switzer Lincoln (Water St), 1924 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Mrs. Cornelia Switzer Burkholder to Mrs. Mary Switzer Lincoln (Water Street, Public Square), 1924 (Box OV 3, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Division of the R.S. Switzer Lot by B.F. Garber, 1924 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Cleo Donovan to John Ramey surveyed No. 9, 1925 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Dr. AW Miller Dec 8, 1925 drawn by AR Myers copy 1 & 2, 1925 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Lot Owned by Cleo Donovan lving on the Northside of Washington St., 1925 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Lots Owned by O.M. Masters, 1925 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Map of C. Donivan's Lots Ashby Park as Re-subdivided (Monroe St, Madison Street), 1925 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - N Main Street of D.B. Masters, City Service No. 1, Southern R.R. siding and Mill Property, 1925 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Plat of lot belonging to the Valley R.R. Co. West of T.N. Haas' residence (Grace St), 1925 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Plat of the property in the north end of Harrisonburg Virginia belonging to O.M. Masters, 1925 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Plat showing 45' Street as laid out in a division of part of the land belonging to the Est. of R. Kyle dec. 1868, 1925 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Plat showing 45' Street as laid out in a division of part of the land belonging to the Est. of R. Kyle dec. 1868, 1925 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - City of Harrisonburg Proposed Plan for Widening Grace St. Through the Land of C.-W.R.R. Co., 1926 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - J.C. Staples to Ward Garber and Others (Mason St, West View Street), 1926 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Map of Lot to be conveyed to C.C. Conrad and John P. Burke by Mrs. Kate S. Paul (W. Market Street, Liberty Street), 1926 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Map of Lots Laying on the North side of E. Water Street. to be conveyed to E.T. Garber by V.R. Slater and Others, 1926 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Newtown Giant Incubator Corp. to the Buckeye Incubator Co. Harrisonburg VA. (On Back) Daly Bros. Shoe Factory, 1926 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Plat of Lot Lying on the Northside Gratten St. To be conveyed to W.P. Anthony by J.S. Flory (Grattan St, South Main St), 1926 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - City of Harrisonburg proposed plan for Wolfe Street Bridge copy 1 & 2, 1927 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 2)
  - Homeland Addition City of Harrisonburg VA, 1927 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Map of Re-Subdivision of Block #5 in the Brookland Addition to the City of Harrisonburg, VA owned by L.A. Parr and J.P. Burke copy 1, 2 and 3, 1927 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Plat of L Lots Laying in the Ashby Park Addition as Sub-Divided by J.W. Conrad, 1927 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Sub Division of Lots owned by E.G. Weiner and J.C. Conrad being made up of Lots 6-7- and 8 of Block "E" of the Garber and Garber Addition, 1927 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - The Home-land Reality Co to L.A. and D.L. Logan, 1927 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - City of Harrisonburg Proposed Plan Effinger St. Bridge, 1928 (Box OV 1, Folder 3, Container 3, Container 5, Folder 2)
  - City of Harrisonburg Proposed Plan Washington St. Bridge copy 2, 1928 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - City of Harrisonburg VA. Proposed Sewer Extension to N. Liberty St., 1928 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 2)
  - Lots owned by Mrs. Dora M. Schaeffer Laying on the west side of Mason Street, 1928 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Map Harrisonburg Ice Corporation Property Harrisonburg VA, 1928 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Map of Houck Tanning Co's Property Laying South of Bruce Street Harrisonburg Virginia as sub-divided, 1928 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Map of Lots owned by C.C. Conrad and Mrs. C.C. Conrad, 1928 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Map of Re-Subdivision of Block No. 5 in the Brookland Addition to the city of Harrisonburg, VA owned by L.A. Parr and J. P. Burke, 1928 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - South Side elevation Laymans Trestle Chesapeake & Western RR Co., 1928 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Map England, Walton and Co's Property Laying North of Bruce Street Harrisonburg Virginia, 1929 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 2)
  - Map Isaac Ney's Property Laying on the East Side Main Street Harrisonburg Virginia, 1929 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Map Mrs. Dora M. Shaeffer's property laying north of Campbell and West of Mason Street Harrisonburg Virginia, 1929 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Map of lots owned by J.A. and C.O. Conrad laying on the South side of Effinger Street Harrisonburg VA, 1929 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Map of the Valley of Virginia Milk Producers Ass'n Property- Laying south of Washington Street Harrisonburg Virginia, 1929 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - Map E.L. Foley's Property Harrisonburg Virginia (East Market Street, Wolf Street, Rock Street, Gay Street), 1929 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 2)
  - Grading Plan for North Athletic Field Harrisonburg VA copy 1 & 2, 1930 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Map Mrs. Lucile R. Yancey's Property Laying on Both sides of East Market Street Harrisonburg Virginia, 1930 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Map of 1.157 Acres of Land lying on the South Side of Grace Street. Harrisonburg VA to be conveyed to the Rockingham County Farm Bureau by the Chesapeake Western Railway, 1930 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Map of property owned by John W. Morrison situated on the south side of Bruce Street Harrisonburg VA, 1930 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Map of Property Owned by the Central Atlantic States Service Corp. Harrisonburg Virginia, 1930 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Map of the Mutual Milling & Supply Corp's Property Situated on the East side of North Liberty Street Harrisonburg Virgina, 1930 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Map showing land leased by the Texas Oil Co from the Chesapeake and Western RR Harrisonburg VA copy 1 & 2, 1930 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Map Showing Land Leased by the Twin City Oil and Gas Corporation from S.H. Branum Harrisonburg VA, 1930 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Map of Lot Situated on the South Side of Warsaw Street Harrisonburg VA. to be Leased to Harry E. Garber by the Chesapeake Western Railway, 1931 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Map of Lots No. 9-10-11-12-13 of the Brock and Myers 2nd Addition to the City of Harrisonburg Virginia as subdivided by the Harrisonburg Building and Supply co., Inc., 1931 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Map of the A.M. Lowenbach Lot situated on the West Side of South High Street Harrisonburg Virginia (West Water St), 1931 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Map of the Fannie Smith Lot Situated on the South Side of Reservoir Street Harrisonburg VA Showing Proposed Division Lines Between Same and the Anderson Barber Estate, 1931 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Strip of Land to be conveyed by the Massanutten Farms Hatchery to the City of Harrisonburg, 1931 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Strip of Land to be Conveyed by the Massanutten Farms Hatchery to the City of Harrisonburg (Main St and Masters), 1931 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Strip of Land to be Conveyed to the City of Harrisonburg by Chas. B. Dallard (Gay St, Sterling St, Kelley St), 1931 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Map of Parcel of Land Owned by Jno. Mitchell's Estate Required by City of Harrisonburg For Street Improvements copy 1 & 2, 1932 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Map of Proposed Plan for Widening E. Market Street through the land of Jos. T. Houck, 1932 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Map of Strip of Land owned by H.M. Newman and Others Required by the City of Harrisonburg For Street Improvement, Alta Vista copy 1 & 2, 1932 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Map Showing Proposed 30' Street Leading From Grace Street to West Bruce Street Harrisonburg VA copy 1 & 2, 1932 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 2)
  - Map of Proposed Plan for Widening E. Market St., 1933 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Map of Proposed Plan for Widening E. Market St. Through the Land of L.E. Spindle etc., 1933 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Map of Warsaw Street To Be Dedicated to the City of Harrisonburg For Public Use Also Showing Proposed Right of Way "A" and "B" For Ingress and Egress to City Owned Property, 1933 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Map showing proposed plan for widening S. High Street copy 1 & 2, 1933 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 2)
  - Plan of Strip of Land Required by the City of Harrisonburg from the Grattan-E St., 1933 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Plat of Land to be Conveyed to the City of Harrisonburg VA. By John Gray Paul, 1933 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Plat of Land to be conveyed to the City of Harrisonburg VA. By John Gray Paul, 1933 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Plat of Strip of Land Required by City of Harrisonburg VA from D.H. Liskey to Widen Old Furnace Road, 1933 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Plat of Strip of Land Required by City of Harrisonburg VA. From D.H. Liskey to Widen Old Furnance Road, 1933 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Plat of Strip of Land Required by the City of Harrisonburg from the Grattan E. St. (Ott Street, Campbell Street), 1933 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Plat of Strip of Land Required by The City of Harrisonburg from the Grattan Est. (Ott St, Campbell St), 1933 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Proposed Storm Water Control at R.R. Hisey's Property (Wolfe St), 1933 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Proposed Storm Water Control at R.R. Hisey's Property (Wolfe Street), 1933 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Plat of Lot Laying on the North Side of Hawkins Street. Harrisonburg VA Owned By the Chas. Fields Est. And Purchased by C.P. Williams for Taxes, 1934 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Profile of Blacks Run, Part A, 1934 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Profile of Blacks Run, Part B, 1934 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Profile of Blacks Run, Part C, 1934 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Profile of Blacks Run, Part D, 1934 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Profile of Blacks Run, Part E, 1934 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Profile Sub-merged Dam Harrisonburg VA, 1934 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 2)
  - Proposed New Street as Petioned for by N. Wilson Davis and Others (Mason Street, Campbell Street, Paul Street, Ott Street) copy 1 & 2, 1934 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - City of Harrisonburg proposed 6" sewer and water lines, 1935 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - City of Harrisonburg Proposed 6" Sewer and Water lines (Main St. and Old Port Republic Road), 1935 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Map of Proposed Plan for Widening Rock Street copy 1 & 2, 1935 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Map of Proposed Street Extension from Main St. to Kratzer Rd., copy 1 & 2, 1935 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 3)
  - Map of Strip of Land Required by the City of Harrisonburg to Widen N. Main St. Through the Land of W.M. Joseph, 1935 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Map of Strip of Land Required By the City of Harrisonburg To Widen N. Main St. Through the Lands of Wm. M. Joseph and Flossie Fultz, 1935 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Municipal Swimming Pool Harrisonburg Virginia, copy 1 & 2, 1935 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 3)
  - Plan of Company Area State Military Reservation, 1935 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 3)
  - Plat of Lots No. 14-15 in Block 1 of the Sibert, Brock-Myers, And Staples Additon to the City of Harrisonburg Virginia (Grattan Street), 1935 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Plat of Property Owned by Dr. J.R. Gambill Located At Harrisonburg VA As Divided Into Two Lots, 1935 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Plat of Property to be Conveyed to the Harrisonburg Building and Supply Co. By the Executor of the Wilbur L. Moorland Dec'd Est. Located at Harrisonburg VA, 1935 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Plat of the Chandler Property at Harrisonburg VA to be Conveyed to the City of Harrisonburg by A.H. Chandler, 1935 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Plat of the Whetzel Seed Company's Property Located at Harrisonburg Rockingham County Virginia (Valley Railroad, W. Market St), 1935 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Plat showing proposed Widening of North Main Street. Harrisonburg VA Over the Property of Mrs. Ethel Swartz, 1935 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Proposed plan for widening and extending Wolfe Street copy 1 & 2, 1935 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Proposed Site For Armory Harrisonburg Virginia, 1935 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Public Square, North Main St., 1935 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 3)
  - Typical Section Blacks Run Project City of Harrisonburg copy 1 & 2, 1935 (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - City of Harrisonburg Plan for Improving West Market Street, 1936 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 3)
  - City of Harrisonburg Proposed Site Colored School, 1936 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 3)
  - City of Harrisonburg West Market Street Grade West of Willow St., 1936 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 3)
  - Corrected Map of the Sibert Addition Which is Recorded in D.B. 137 Page 460 and the Myers-Brock-Staples Addition Recorded in D.B. 122 Page 53 Harrisonburg Virginia, 1936 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 3)
  - Map of proposed plan for widening E. Wolfe Street copy 1 & 2, 1936 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - Map of Storm Water Conditions on Wolfe Street, 1936 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - Map Showing Exchange of Land between the City of Harrisonburg and John P. Burke (Harrison St.), 1936 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Map Showing Exchange of Land Between The City of Harrisonburg and John P. Burke copy 1 & 2, 1936 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - Plat of Lot to be Conveyed to E.D. Ott by the City of Harrisonburg VA copy 1 & 2, 1936 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Sewer Through the Land of J.H. Hoy and Others (Sterling Street, Rock Street, Gay Street, and Hill Street), 1936 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - Strip of Land to be Conveyed to the City of Harrisonburg by John P. Burke, 1936 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - Tract of Land to be Conveyed by John P. Burke to City of Harrisonburg copy 1 & 2, 1936 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - Tract of Land to be Conveyed by John P. Burke to the City of Harrisonburg (Gay St, Mt. Clinton Pike), 1936 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Tract of Land to be Conveyed by John P. Burke to the City of Harrisonburg (Gay Street and Mt. Clinton Pike), 1936 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Tract of Land to be Conveyed by John P. Burke to the City of Harrisonburg (Gay Street, Mt. Clinton Pike), 1936 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - City of Harrisonburg Virginia Johnson Street Sewer, 1937 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - Department of the Interior U.S. Geological Survey Virginia, Elkton Quadrangle, 1937 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - Map of Edge Lawn Annex 1937 copy 1 & 2, 1937 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - Map of Strip of Land to be Conveyed to the City of Harrisonburg (Academy St, Bruce St, S.High St.), 1937 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Map of Strip of Land to be Conveyed to the City of Harrisonburg (Academy St, W Bruce St, S.High St. ), 1937 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Map of Water Lines Owned by the City of Harrisonburg Virginia to be Adjusted Due to Construction of New Highway copy 1, 1937 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 3)
  - Map of Water Lines Owned by the City of Harrisonburg Virginia to be Adjusted Due to Construction of New Highway copy 2, 1937 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - W-P-A Projects City of Harrisonburg Virginia Plan of Johnson and Washington Street Sewers copy 1 & 2, 1937 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - W-P-A- Projects City of Harrisonburg Virginia Plan of Johnson and Washington Street Sewers, 1937 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Plat of Proposed Sewer Lines Leading From the Eastern Mennonite School to Harrisonburg Virginia, 1938 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - Map of the Lawrence Leather Company Property to be Conveyed to the City of Harrisonburg copy 1 & 2, 1939 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 3)
  - Plat of Property Located at Harrisonburg Virginia to be Conveyed to the Harrisonburg Telephone Company by R.F. Carver and others, 1939 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - Plat of R.E. Lee's Property Situated at Harrisonburg Virginia (West Water St., Elm St.), 1939 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Proposed Plan for Widening Water Street, 1939 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Sewer Through Land of R.S. Monger, 1939 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - United State Dept of Interior Geological survey VA Waynesboro Quadrangle, 1939 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - (Item 1) Plat of W.E. Fry's Property Situated at Harrisonburg Virginia (South Main Street, Weaver Avenue, Dale St.), 1939 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - (Item 2) Plat of Mrs. Clara Belle Fry's Property Located at Harrisonburg Virginia as Surveyed and Sub-divided into Lots, 1949 (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - Concrete Walkway Over Blacks Run, 1940 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 3)
  - Harrisonburg Mutual Telephone Company proposed elimination of overhead wires on Mt. Clinton Pike, 1940 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Improvement proposed at the High School Grounds, 1940 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Map of Park View copy 1 & 2, 1940 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Mt. Clinton Pike Grade, 1940 (Storage 1, Box 1)
  - Plat of O.R. Liskey's Addition to the city of Harrisonburg, 1940 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Plat of property situated at Harrisonburg to be conveyed to E.L. Klingstein by heirs of Sullivan, 1940 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Plat of the Maplehurst Avenue Additon to the City of Harrisonburg Situated at Harrisonburg Virginia Owned by the Heirs of H.M. Newman Dec'd Estate, 1940 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Plat showing block between Paul Street and Grattan Street, 1940 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Proposed plan for improving Mt. Clinton Pike, 1940 (Container 3, Container 5, Folder 3)
  - Municipal building complex with parking lot copy 1 & 2, 1941 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth Street. proposed curb between Liberty Street and Main Street, 1941 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Lawn Ave. Sewer, 1941 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Plat of Property situated At Harrisonburg Virginia Belonging to Leona F. Mundy, Janet lee Miller, Rebecca Gene Miller, and Mary Eleanor Miller as Surveyed and Divided Into Lots, 1941 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Plat showing proposed extension of 30' Street leading from Grace Street to the intersection of Warsaw Street, 1941 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Proposed Sewer Extension Ott Street copy 1 & 2, 1941 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Plat of John R. Grattan and Margaret S. Weaver's property, 1942 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Plat of Property Located at Harrisonburg VA Belonging to Rolland H. Berry, 1943 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Plat of Property Owned By the City of Harrisonburg Situated at Harrisonburg Virginia (South Liberty Street) copy 1 & 2, 1943 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Proposed Coal Trestle, Part A, 1943 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Proposed Coal Trestle, Part B, 1943 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Proposed Coal Trestle, Part C, 1943 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Proposed Plan for bridge at Rock Street, 1943 (Map-case 3, Drawer 5, Folder 3)
  - Proposed plan for Bridge Chesapeake Ave, Harrisonburg, 1943 (Map-case 3, Drawer 5, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Coal Trestle For Harrisonburg detail of features copy 1 & 2, 1944 (Map-case 3, Drawer 5, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Coal Trestle for Harrisonburg Virginia Location Plan copy 1 & 2, 1944 (Map-case 3, Drawer 5, Folder 3)
  - Map of Industrial Site for Sale by the City of Harrisonburg (Patterson Street, Warsaw Street, S.Main Street), 1945 (Map-case 3, Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - Map of industrial site for sale by the city of Harrisonburg, Harrisonburg VA (Patterson Street, Warsaw Street, South Main Street), 1945 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Map of Silver Lake Dayton Virginia Owned by the City of Harrisonburg copy 1, 2, 3, 4, & 5, 1945 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Maplehurst Addition Harrisonburg VA, 1945 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Plat of Property owned by Cassco Refrigerating Corp and the Shell Cash Coal Co. Inc., 1945 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Proposed plan for the improvement of Rock and Gay Street, 1945 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Massanutten Heights, 1946 (Map-case 3, Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - Plat of George D. Conrad's Property Situated at Harrisonburg Virginia as Surveyed and Divided into Lots (Garden St, Crawford Avenue), 1946 (Box OV 3, Drawer 2)
  - Plat of Mrs. Willie I. Sullivan's Property Located at Harrisonburg Virginia as surveyed and divided into lots (Myrtle St, East Rock Street), 1946 (Box OV 2, Drawer 2)
  - Plat of property located at Harrisonburg Virginia owned by Laurence J. Purcell and James R. Purcell (Federal St.), 1946 (Box OV 2, Drawer 2)
  - Plat of Property situated at Harrisonburg Virginia to be conveyed to the Harrisonburg Coca-Cola Bottling Works Inc. by Mrs. Sadie M. Joseph, 1946 (Box OV 2, Drawer 2)
  - Plat of the Hebrew Friendship Congregation's Harrisonburg, Jewish cemetery, 1946 (Box OV 2, Drawer 2)
  - Plat of the J.T. Houck "Residence" Property Situated at Harrisonburg Virginia (East Water St, East Market St), 1946 (Box OV 2, Drawer 2)
  - City of Harrisonburg proposed extension of Grace Street, copy 1 & 2, 1947 (Map-case 3, Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - Map of 16" Water Line from Riven Rock to Rawley Springs, 1947 (Map-case 3, Drawer 6, Folder 6)
  - Map of Land to be Acquired by the City of Harrisonburg copy 1 & 2, 1947 (Box OV 2, Drawer 2)
  - Map of Proposed 16" Pipe Line from Dale Enterprise to Silver Lake (U.S. Route 33), 1947 (Storage 1, Box 1)
  - Plat of Property Located at Harrisonburg VA Belonging to Rolland H. Berry, 1947 (Box OV 2, Folder 2)
  - Proposed Extension of Grace Street, copy 1 & 2, 1947 (Map-case 3, Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - Proposed Plan for Pumping Station at Silver Lake copy 1, 2, & 3, 1947 (Box OV 2, Folder 2)
  - Sketch showing a section of the Woodbine Cemetery (Resevoir St), 1947 (Box OV 2, Folder 2)
  - Plat of Earl H. Wetsel's Addition to the city of Harrisonburg, 1948 (Box OV 2, Folder 2)
  - Plat of Ethel Irvin Line Weaver's Property Located at Harrisonburg Virginia (East Water St), 1948 (Box OV 2, Folder 2)
  - Plat of Property Located at Harrisonburg Virginia to be conveyed to Bruner Ray Fox and Joe Howard Fox By Lula K Rife, 1948 (Box OV 2, Folder 2)
  - Plat of property located at Harrisonburg Virginia to be conveyed to J.S. Denton and Sons by L.E. Friddle, 1948 (Box OV 2, Folder 2)
  - Proposed Bridge Site North Main Street, 1948 (Map-case 3, Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - City of Harrisonburg proposed extension of Grace Street, 1949 (Box OV 2, Folder 2)
  - City of Harrisonburg Proposed Water Line Connection on the property of Samuel Heatwole, 1949 (Box OV 2, Folder 2)
  - City of Harrisonburg Standard Meter Cover, 1949 (Box OV 2, Folder 2)
  - Plat of Property Located At Harrisonburg Virginia to be conveyed to Geo. C. Grattan III, John R. Grattan and Mrs. Margaret G. Weaver by Mrs. Frances R. Grattan (W. Water St, South Main St), 1949 (Box OV 2, Folder 2)
  - Plat of the Eastern Portion of Block 2 of the Fairview Addition to the City of harrisonburg Va. As Re-subdivided by E.S. Purcell (Bluestone street, Monument Avenue), 1949 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Proposed Bridge Site North Main Street; (On Back) N Main Drainage 10, 1949 (Box OV 2, Folder 2)
  - Proposed plan for widening Gay Street, 1949 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Map of Proposed Annexation (High Street, Sunrise Avenue), 1950 (Box OV 2, Folder 3)
  - Map of Proposed Annexation, film (High St, Sunrise Avenue), 1950 (Box OV 2, Folder 3)
  - Plat of Carl L and Antoinette Spitzer's property located at Harrisonburg VA, 1950 (Box OV 2, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Annexation to City of Harrisonburg copy 1 & 2, 1950 (Map-case 3, Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - Strip of Land Required to Widen Franklin St. copy 1 & 2, 1950 (Box OV 2, Folder 3)
  - Central Mills Inc to City, Keister School Property (South High Street, South Avenue), 1951 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)